Baby Gupta

MERN: Full Stack Web Developer



+91 8766946031 • Mumbai

</> Profile

As a Full Stack MERN developer, I deliver end-toend web solutions with analytical thinking, creativity, and reliability. I stay updated with the latest technology trends and work well in crossfunctional teams. I am committed to exceeding expectations by delivering innovative solutions on time and to the highest standards.I look forward to the opportunity to contribute my skills and expertise to your organization.

Professional Experience

Operation executive, *infosys ⊘* 05/2021 - present

Proctor, Enfuse solution pvt ltd 03/2020 - 04/2021 | mumbai, india

{} TECHNICAL SKILLS

React, Html, Javascript, Css, Redux, Chakra UI, Node js, Express js, MongoDB, Data structure and Algorithm

SOFT SKILL

Collaboration | Critical thinking Adaptability | Communication

Projects

IKEA CLONE.

A fullstack web app clone of IKEA. ⊘ Github ∂

Areas of Responsibility:

- merging
- deployment

Feature:

- login
- homepage
- header
- footer

TechStack:

- React
- redux
- · chakra UI

FABALLEY CLONE,

Faballey E-commerce website clone. ∂ Github ∂

Areas of Responsibility:

GitHub management

Feature:

- User update
- Logout
- Wishlist

TechStack:

- Html
- Javascript
- Css

PHARMEASY CLONE,

Pharmeasy website clone *⊘* Github ∂

Areas of Responsibility:

meet scheduling

Feature:

- Home page
- · product detail page

TechStack:

- Html
- Javascript
- Css

Education

MERN Full stack development, Masai school 09/2022 - present

Bsc It, Annasaheb vartak college (Mumbai University) *∂* 2017 - 2020 | mumbai, India